I don't think you realize
what a godsend you are.
Excuse me.
Not many people jump
at the opportunity to stay here alone.
- Why?
- Old ghost stories.
This is the oldest house
in the city, you know.
Lots of history. A few unpleasant nicknames.
We've tried to rebuild the reputation
in the neighborhood, but then...
...last winter the caretaker, well...
Yes?
Well, I really shouldn't be telling you this.
Please.
Well, poor girl, she... she threw
herself off the upstairs balcony.
- Why did she do that?
- Hard to say, really.
But you needn't worry about that.
This really is a lovely old house.
It will take care of you, and I'm certain
there won't be a single problem.
- Of course not, ma'am.
- Good.
- Will a check be alright?
- Yes.
Splendid. I mustn't keep them waiting.
I left our telephone number by the phone.
Feel free to call any time
about anything, even to say hello.
- I will.
- You're a doll. Toodle-oo.
Darling.
Poor girl.
She threw herself off the upstairs balcony.
Yes?
Hello?
- Darling, is that you?
- Yes, ma'am.
I wanted to check in and make sure
the first night went smoothly.
Yes, everything's fine.
I forgot to mention to you, please,
have your references reach out to us.
- Who?
- Andrew Dopling or something.
- Abbott?
- Yes, that's it.
They were odd. I'll try them for you.
I still haven't received
my final payment from them anyway.
Just give them the number
I left for you. Goodbye, dear.
Ma'am, there's one room
that I can't get into.
Yes?
The room at the end of the hall.
I don't have a key.
Don't concern yourself with that room, dear.
- Is that understood?
- Well, I...
It must remain locked at all times.
Am I clear?
Yes, ma'am.
- Thank you again. Goodbye, dear!
- Ma'am?
Miss?
Miss? Oh, God!
Jesus, I'm sorry. Sorry.
I just... you dropped this.
Here.
Sorry for frightening you.
Okay. Alright then. Bye.
Hell...
Hello?
Hello? Hello? Hello, are you there?
Hi. Can I...
- Thanks.
- Is anybody sitting here?
- No.
- Do you mind if I sit?
Now I'm not...
...interrupting anything, am I?
What do you mean?
I just hope your boyfriend doesn't come
and hit me in the back of the head.
Don't worry.
Have you... been here before?
Why?
You know, I don't know. Maybe I'm mistaken.
What do you mean?
I just... I guess you look familiar.
I just have one of those faces.
Yeah. Yeah, I guess so.
Hey, can I get you something?
Like what?
A drink.
Let me get two gins.
Do you like gin?
Sure.
Very nice.
Thank you.
You're sure you're not waiting for anybody?
I was waiting for you.
That's funny.
- It's true.
- It's also very flattering.
Tell you what, I am gonna get another round.
You too?
Let me get two more.
Why not?
So what do you do for work?
For work, your job?
Nothing, really.
Would you excuse me for a moment?
- Where're you going?
- I'll be right back.
- Don't go anywhere.
- Okay.
You alright?
- Yes. Don't I look alright?
- Yeah, you look great.
- Thank you.
- I'm just waiting for another drink.
- I don't know where the bartender is.
- Do you want to come back to my place?
- What?
- It's not far.
There's plenty of brandy.
It's free.
Yeah.
Yeah, let me just cash out.
Alright. Let's go.
Are you joking?
Are you coming?
This is your place?
You can sit here.
Oh, my God!
You know, I gotta tell you, I never
pictured you living in a place like this.
Why not?
Well, because...
I'm sorry.
Well, they have got to tell you this kind
of thing before you move in, right?
That it's haunted?
Okay.
So they must've gave you
a big discount, or...
...something like that which is
obviously none of my business, but...
No. Please.
I mean, it's just stories I heard
when I was growing up.
But basically, they used
to tell us about this...
...old lunatic.
Used to live here...
...perform these rituals
in one of the back rooms.
Trying to conjure up the living devil
or something like that.
It was kids' stories, mostly, but...
You grew up here?
Yeah, I grew up
just a few blocks south of here...
...so don't hold that against me.
Hey, you know what?
I gotta be honest with you.
This isn't something
I ever really do with anybody.
The thing is, I just got
this big promotion, so..
Do what?
Whatever it is we're doing.
- We're having a drink.
- Yeah, yeah.
Of course.
It's just...
It's funny, I...
It's just not every day I go out and...
...meet somebody like you who's so open.
This whole city is...
...always on the defensive, and it's just...
...it's refreshing...
...to meet somebody who doesn't
immediately think you're a maniac.
You're one of the good guys.
I try to be.
You're not lying to me?
Hey.
Tell you what...
...does it look like I'm lying?
Just one of those faces, Henry.
What?
No, I'm telling you the truth.
I am honestly one of the good ones.
Look, I waiting for my friends at the bar.
Ask them!
I would never in a million years
just go home with someone I just met...
...who invited me to their house.
If I told them that, and for whiskey?
They would laugh in my face!
I tell you what would be really funny,
we should give them a ring later on...
and tell them... tell them
that it's entirely possible...
...to have a cordial meeting with someone
when you just met them at a bar 'cause...
God.
Why did you come here tonight?
What did you expect?
You didn't even ask me my name.
Did you want to fuck me?
Remember me?
Do you remember me?
Because I remember you, Henry Sullivan.
I remember...
...every single thing...
...about that night.
Why did you do it?
Why did you pick me?
What did I ever do to you?
Answer me!
Fuck you!
Help me.
Help me. Help me.
Hello?
Darling, I want you
to listen to me very carefully.
Ma'am?
We finally got a hold of your references.
- You did?
- Yes.
Dr. Abbott.
Dr. Abbott?
You never cared for his family, did you?
We know what you did, dear.
Darling?
I couldn't let him live
with what he did to me.
But Dr. Abbott...
...he says I'm okay.
He says I'm okay now.
We're not mad, dear.
We would just like you...
we would just like you to leave.
Take your things and leave.
We would just like you to leave.
I saw him...
...walking around.
Henry...
...Sullivan.
I saw him walking around
the street the other day.
Right in front of me.
I couldn't let him live
with what he'd done to me.
Darling?
Yes?
What do you mean you saw him
walking around the other day?
Ma'am?
Did you do something to somebody?
Can you hear me?
- Can you hear me?
- Ma'am?
Yes?
Please just listen to me.
You can keep the money.
- Please, just go home.
- Is it true what they say about this place?
What? Who?
That someone tried to conjure
the devil here once.
That's...
It happened in that room, didn't it?
The one upstairs.
They made me do it.
Ma'am?
I think I'll become one
of your ghost stories now.
What? Hello?
Hello?
What did you make me do it?
- We can't cuff the guy unless...
- She said there was a murder?
I don't know. That's...
- Police. Open up.
- Now we got four guys trying to...
Hey, listen, shut the fuck up! Alright?
- Ma'am, do you have the keys?
- I'm sorry. Jesus! Lighten up, will you?
It's a good story.
Come on...
Hello?
This is the one you were here for...
You can be free.
You don't know how much
of a godsend you are, really.
Well, it was fortunate for me, too.
We didn't know if we were gonna be able
to get somebody at such late notice...
...especially with our reputation.
- Reputation?
- With the previous caretakers.
- What happened?
- Well...
...I really shouldn't be telling you this.